Terrance Cunningham

2721 N Robie ct Spokane Valley 99206 (206) 419-7786 TerranceJCunningham@gmail.com www.terrancecunningham.com

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing in regards to the web designer position offered. Flexibility, effective time management, excellent communication skills, and a strong work ethic are essential for any web designer. These key skills have enabled me to balance education and work, and establish a solid foundation of web design experience. I believe that function and design go hand in hand and enjoy balancing both elements to create a quality interface that meets the needs of the business and the consumer.

I hold a degree in Web Design with additional experience in social networking and content development. Programs that I am proficient with include:

HTML	XHTML	UX Design	Java Script
Access	JQuery	РНР	MS Word
Excel	Flash 5.5	Abode Photo CS5	Abode Illustrator CS5
Dream Weaver			

Web design requires the self motivation to continue education and I look forward to adding logo design to my resume. My past work experience has demanded efficiency, organization, and service excellence. The attached resume will provide a sample of my past achievements and will demonstrate my potential for making a significant contribution to Home Performance Washington. I have enjoyed working with you and your staff and look forward to hearing from you.

If any additional information or clarification is needed, please feel free to contact me. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Terrance Cunningham

Encl: Resume

Terrance Cunningham

Phone: 206-419-7786 Web: www.Terrancecunningham.com E-Mail: TerranceJCunningham.gmail.com

Objective

To obtain a position and utilize my training and experience. To be part of a creative team that will boost profitability for the company.

Skills

- · HTML, XHTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, UX Design, SQL, MYSQL,
- · Adobe Dreamweaver CS5, Adobe Photoshop CS5, Adobe Illustrator CS5, Adobe Flash 5.5
- MS-Office (Word, Excel)
- Wordpress Content Management System (CMS)

Work Experience

Puget Sound Cooperative Credit Union, Seattle WA

(2011-2012)

- · Re-Model and Re-Design to PSCCU website, Social Media System Integration
- · Consulted Client about Work Flow and Scope methods
- Client Staging Area, Tabs Panel displaying lowest rates for customers convenience

Web Design, Seattle WA

(2009-Present)

- · Client Consultations and assistance in regards to website design requirements
- · Created and designed a UX website for a class project
- Designed websites and integrated it on Wordpress for Class Project

Subway, Sales Associate, Seattle WA

(2007-Present)

- · Primary Employee Trainer, Inventory Control, Sales Evaluation,
- · Financial Transactions, Ensure compliance with all Health Code Regulations,
- · Customer Service, Absence coverage at 4 locations

Bainbridge Bakers, Barista/Line Cook, Bainbridge Island WA

(2004-2007)

- · Opened Store and Registers, Prepared all pastries, Inventory Control,
- · Sales Records Reconciliations, Employee Scheduling,
- · Ensure adherence to all OSHA standards and Health Code Regulations

Education

Seattle Central Community College

(2009-Present)

Web Design - I have created and designed websites for class projects utilizing methods such as UX design. I have also participated on a team as a consultant to discuss layouts, design specifications, and to assist with modifications for a live client.

Renton Technical College

(2006-2007)

Phlebotomy Technical Program – I have worked with children and adults for Blood collection, IV therapy precautions, and specimen collection, handling, and processing.